guys this one says factor completely and
this completely is very important it
might be more than just one step so
first let's factor out the GCF the
greatest common factor for the two of
them or we can Factor two out of both of
them we can factor out an X out of both
of them and we can factor out a y
squared out of both of them so now let's
go after this first one two times what
gives us two that's one x times what
gives us x to the fourth that's X cubed
and then y squared times what gives us y
to the fifth that's y cubed so this
times this gives us this and now 2xy
squared times what gives us 2xy squared
well that's just one because this
matches this exactly a lot of people
might think we're done right now but we
can go further this right here is a sum
of cubes a cubed plus B Cubed is equal
to a plus b times a squared minus a B
plus b squared this first term is a
cubed that would mean that a is equal to
the cube root of this which would just
be x y and then for the B we want to
take the cube root of this one because
one is equal to B Cubed and that gives
us one so now we can just plug it right
into this equation so let's copy down
the GC F the 2xy squared and then this
is going to change into two parentheses
we put the a in the first spot which is
x y and then we do plus b in the next
spot and B was one and then for the a
squared we want to square this which
would be x squared y squared we squared
each of the terms and then minus a b so
we're going to minus these two things
multiplied which is just minus x y and
then plus b squared but B squared is
equal to one because one squared is one
and this is the answer to the question
we factored completely how exciting